=Afterlife of Love and Revenge= =Episode 21=
= الآخرة من الحب والانتقام = = الحلقة 21 =
Miss Qiaoyan,
ملكة جمال Qiaoyan ،
listen to our explanation.
استمع إلى شرحنا.
It's okay.
حسنا.
This matter
هذا الامر
is easy to be solved.
من السهل حلها.
I can just leave.
يمكنني فقط المغادرة.
I'm really happy.
أنا سعيد حقا.
Let me be frank to you all.
اسمحوا لي أن أكون صريحا معكم جميعا.
Actually, I have someone I love.
في الواقع ، لدي شخص أحبه.
Also, I'm planning to elope with him.
كما أنني أخطط للهروب معه.
I was afraid to hurt Mr. Chu.
كنت خائفة من إيذاء السيد تشو.
This is great.
هذا عظيم.
I'm leaving now.
انا راحل الان.
I wish you all the happiness.
وأتمنى لكم كل السعادة.
I wish you all the happiness, too.
أتمنى لك كل السعادة أيضًا.
Qiaoyan.
كياويان.
Come back if you're not happy.
عد إذا لم تكن سعيدًا.
Let me know that you're safe.
اسمحوا لي أن أعرف أنك بأمان.
Jingyu, I got it.
جينغيو ، فهمت.
I'm leaving now.
انا راحل الان.
Okay.
تمام.
Take care of yourself.
اعتنِ بنفسك.
(How do I explain to my father?)
(كيف اشرح لوالدي؟)
Such an unfilial daughter.
هذه ابنة غير متحيزة.
Father.
أب.
You rascal.
أنت الوغد.
You only told me now.
أنت فقط أخبرتني الآن.
You can't even stop a woman from leaving.
لا يمكنك حتى منع المرأة من المغادرة.
No way.
مستحيل.
I need to send someone to catch Qiaoyan back.
أحتاج إلى إرسال شخص ما للقبض على Qiaoyan.
I can't let her do whatever she likes.
لا يمكنني السماح لها بفعل ما تشاء.
Master.
يتقن.
I realised that Mr. Chu and his servant, Longyue,
أدركت أن السيد تشو وخادمه لونجيوي
are having an affair.
هم على علاقة غرامية.
Father.
أب.
Listen to me. That's not the case.
استمع لي.  هذا ليس هو الحال.
I'll handle this matter.
سأتعامل مع هذا الأمر.
Get back to work.
عد الى العمل.
Father.
أب.
You still have me,
لازلت معك،
right?
الصحيح؟
Let me handle this. Don't worry.
دعني اتعامل مع ذلك.  لا تقلق.
This is great.
هذا عظيم.
Ask Longyue
اسأل Longyue
to hold Chu Yuzhi.
لعقد Chu Yuzhi.
I can then send some to catch Qiaoyan
يمكنني بعد ذلك إرسال البعض للقبض على Qiaoyan
back.
الى الخلف.
Father, that's not what I meant.
أبي ، هذا ليس ما قصدته.
I didn't expect that.
لم أتوقع ذلك.
I didn't expect that either.
لم أتوقع ذلك أيضًا.
Dear,
عزيزي،
I think Qiaoyan eloped dashingly.
أعتقد أن Qiaoyan هرب بشكل متقطع.
Why not...
لما لا...
Why not we elope, too?
لماذا لا نهرب أيضا؟
No way.
مستحيل.
My husband is destined to become the Deputy Chancellor.
زوجي مقدر أن يصبح نائب المستشار.
The imperial examination is more important.
الامتحان الامبراطوري أكثر أهمية.
Great.
رائعة.
I've finally got the evidence.
لقد حصلت أخيرًا على الدليل.
Someone, come here!
شخص ما ، تعال إلى هنا!
The two adulterers are about to elope!
الزانيان على وشك الفرار!
Master!
يتقن!
Why are you shouting here?
لماذا تصرخ هنا؟
Master,
يتقن،
look at how shameless they are.
انظروا كيف هم وقحون.
I just heard about how
لقد سمعت للتو عن كيف
they're going to elope.
سوف يهربون.
Don't be ridiculous.
لا تكن سخيفا.
You didn't hear anything.
لم تسمع شيئًا.
You've been in the Chancellor's residence for so long.
لقد كنت في مقر إقامة المستشار لفترة طويلة.
Haven't you learned of
لم تعلم بها
what not to interfere with?
ما لا تتدخل فيه؟
From today onwards,
من اليوم فصاعدا،
get out from my residence.
اخرج من مسكني.
You can never step in here anymore.
لا يمكنك الدخول هنا بعد الآن.
Master, I was wrong.
سيدي ، كنت مخطئا.
Miss Longyue.
ملكة جمال Longyue.
Mr. Chu.
السيد.  تشو.
Please help me to talk to Master.
الرجاء مساعدتي في التحدث إلى المعلم.
Madam Zhang,
سيدتي تشانغ ،
you're old.
انت عجوز.
It's time for you go back to your hometown.
حان الوقت للعودة إلى مسقط رأسك.
Did you hear what Miss Longyue said?
هل سمعت ما قالته الآنسة لونجيو؟
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
Yes.
نعم.
♪You're the fated love coming from the immortal world♪
أنت الحب المقدّر الآتي من العالم الخالد
♪You tie the red strings on the tips of my fingers♪
♪ تقوم بربط الخيوط الحمراء على أطراف أصابعي ♪
♪My heart won't change even if time passes♪
♪ قلبي لن يتغير حتى لو مر الوقت
♪I'll wait for the love in the old place as promised♪
♪ سأنتظر الحب في المكان القديم كما وعدت ♪